All right!
I finally obtained the disc
that contains Star Platinum!
Jolene Kujo,
is it possible she defeated that incumbent
guard and took the disc all by herself?
I'm gonna get my dad's
disc out of this prison,
and that includes the one
Palesnake's holding on to.
Just watch.
Of course,
I erased all knowledge of myself from
Mirachan's memory disc, an obvious choice.
And therefore, nobody can reach me.
The true difference between a
human and an animal is nothing less
than whether or not they desire
to go to heaven after they die.
People should live their lives in such a
manner that they'll be led into heaven.
For that is the beauty inherent
in the nature of humankind.
I don't want to say it!
Let's go!
1, 2, 3 Come and find a way!
Break out without me, you
keep up but long guy
I'm going to use the phone now, right?
Ah?
Are you insane, girl?
Get that gun out of my
face or I'll beat you.
Oh, my mistake.
Please sit down so your
feet don't get tired.
By the way, here's a
cold can of cola for you.
Enjoy your drink.
Come again any time.
This is the Speedwagon Foundation
headquarters in Dallas, Texas.
Please be advised, we don't
accept collect calls on this line.
But I looked in the phone book.
This is all I could find.
Just listen for one second.
I'm an inmate incarcerated at the
Green Dolphin Street prison in Florida.
And my name is Jolene Cujo.
Please connect me to somebody
who knows what that means.
Please hold.
Sorry for the wait.
Are you the daughter of Professor
Jotaro Kujo? And you are?
I'm just a Foundation representative.
Also, so you know, I'm not a stand user.
Oh.
Still, you clearly know
about stands, though.
Do you happen to know
anything about discs?
Yes, of course.
After Dr.
Jotaro Kujo's body was retrieved from the
UUV, he wasn't transferred here to Dallas.
Nevertheless, rest assured, his body
is being sheltered in a safe area.
However, it's really rather
unfortunate, you see.
But there are, well, no signs
of life, medically speaking.
Shit.
Would you believe me
that he could be revived?
I'm merely a scientist.
I can't...
I've obtained one disc. I have it.
He'll come back to life.
I'm certain that my father will
definitely regenerate with this.
I want to give the Foundation
this disc by any means necessary,
but I don't know how.
You need to come up with an idea.
I want to get the disc out of this prison.
Immediately.
Excuse me, miss, but isn't this
call being recorded by the prison?
Yes, it probably is.
Trust me, I'm fully aware
of that possibility.
But I have no time, sir.
It's extremely urgent.
It's now or never.
I'm in an unbelievably
dangerous situation.
I can't safely hide the disc anywhere.
There's gotta be a way for this to work.
Just so you know, though, I'm
not allowed to have any visitors.
I understand.
If you insist.
Meet in the courtyard.
In the courtyard?
You talking about the one sandwiched
between the women's and men's prisons?
Exactly, that's the one.
If you can meet us there in 20
minutes, I think I have an idea.
Wait.
Get there in 20 minutes?
From right now?
Yes.
It's urgent, isn't it?
If you want us to collect the disk,
we will do so with the utmost effort.
If you say he'll be revived,
then we believe you.
However,
you must understand that we are an
unarmed chemotherapy research association.
As a result,
the Speedwagon Foundation
cannot help you escape
from the prison or
protect you from any harm.
Still willing to take the risk
and come to the courtyard?
Yes. I'll go.
So, how exactly do I get it to you?
We shouldn't discuss that
matter over the phone.
All I can say is, please
look for Savage Guardian.
It'll make sense there.
How about we call this
Operation Savage Guardian?
Savage Guardian?
Is that a thing?
Or a person?
Whatever.
I'll figure it out.
I gotta head to the courtyard.
From Floor One's cafeteria.
In order to get to the courtyard,
first I have to go through that
gate, then walk upstairs in the back,
and finally, cross over
the connecting corridor?
on the second floor into the medical wing.
You may go through. Huh?
You're FE40536.
You're the nuisance who was
sent to the punishment cell.
You're restricted from accessing
certain parts of the prison.
Huh?
Jolene!
Emporio! Here!
Don't touch the baseball!
Huh?
I can't let anyone see me. Come on.
Hey, Emporio, who are those guys?
Oh, don't worry, they're not enemies.
He'd prefer to sleep in a bed, of course!
But unfortunately for him, there simply
isn't one to be found in this room.
So naturally, he's got no other choice
but to sleep in the grand piano.
Jolene, this spot is the
ghost room I call home.
It's the place where I live.
A ghost room?
Wait, are you a ghost?
Of course not, Jolene.
Neither of us are ghosts.
We're both actual living humans.
Go ahead and touch me.
I have a body temperature and a pulse.
Listen carefully.
It's not like this room
is inhabited by a ghost.
Rather, the room is a ghost.
Huh?
Would you understand if I
say they're ghost objects?
The Green Dolphin Street
Prison caught fire
in 1984 and then underwent
a huge renovation.
This room was one part of the
prison which completely burned down.
We're inside objects of the past,
the ghost of the music room itself.
Wait, so...
Emporia, wouldn't this
mean that you're a...
that you are a...
I was born like this, with the
ability to use these ghost objects.
Interacting with them is my stand power.
Although, they're the
only things I can use.
So, for example, even this chocolate
bar and Florida orange juice...
I can't actually eat either of them.
I can taste them, though.
They're pretty good.
The heck?
Don't worry, Jolene.
That little clock got stopped
when the prison was burnt down.
There is still time until
that meeting in 20 minutes.
However...
You're discussing how to sneak the
disc out of this prison over the phone.
How could you be so dumb?
I understand that you're
in a difficult situation,
but Pale Snake is definitely going
to learn about your scheme now.
Then please, Emporio, I need you to tell
me a shortcut to get me to the courtyard.
Hey, don't misunderstand me, Jolene.
It's not as if this
ghost room is connected
everywhere all throughout
the prison complex.
I'm just employing the ghost items
which I can use my stand power
to interact with in order to move
around without getting caught.
Like this, you see?
Nonetheless, I know we have to do this.
He wants to tag along with you.
It'd be a good idea to let him.
He'll be a great help.
I forgot to mention, his
name is Weather Forecast.
So this is the present-day music room?
You can let your guard
down with Weather Forecast.
The reason why he doesn't talk much
is because he lost his memories.
Memories?
He doesn't have any
memory of his childhood,
or even how he ended up
inside of the prison.
But he has to serve a
sentence of six years.
He likes to stretch out
and walk on his toes.
He loves reading TV guides,
but he doesn't watch TV.
Whenever he does speak,
he doesn't open his mouth very wide,
so he tends to talk right
in front of your face.
Oh, and his nose breath is warm.
Wait, so does this mean...
Hail snake stole weather
forecast memories probably so
because of this he wants to
find out who he really is?
Also weather forecast
wants to help figure out
why your father's memory
disk was stolen from him!
He said he isn't the
sort of stand user who
has been created with a
disk so it sounds like!
Weather forecast was born
a stand user his power.
...is to alter and control
weather phenomenon.
It's named...
...Weather Forecast.
Just act like you didn't notice.
Pretend.
Well, seems someone was surprised by
the sound and looked inside of the room.
I was able to confirm this.
It would appear that there's somebody
who knows you're making a move.
And they've come here to check up on you.
And now, I've seen the enemy's face.
Oh, so cool!
Oh, shit!
I had no idea he was already
this close to us all!
But if that guy is a stand user,
then we're going to have to take
care of him right now, this instant!
Don't do it, Jolene!
It's better to hide from him!
Keep on running!
He doesn't know that you're trying to
make your way over to the courtyard.
Think about it,
he only came to find us because he must not
know what you talked about on the phone.
If he knew what your plan was, then you
would have headed directly to the courtyard.
That's why he's chasing after us right
now instead of trying to beat us there.
Who the hell is that freak?
We've gotta turn that corner.
Hurry before it catches up to us.
I was correct.
Apparently, hiding was a really good idea.
That weird man doesn't seem to have any
clue about where it is you're heading to.
But what the hell was going
on with that guy anyways?
The way he ran on all
fours was so strange.
We were pretty lucky.
Good thing the dude was still
slower than us regardless.
Still, you should make your way over to
that courtyard as soon as you possibly can.
The phone call you made to the Speedwagon
Foundation was definitely recorded,
but I get the feeling Palesnake
hasn't actually heard that yet.
Quicker you go, less dangerous it'll be.
Medical wing's over there.
Once you make your way
past the medical wing,
there's a gate for the
corridor around the corner.
It leads towards the factory
and then to the men's
prison across the courtyard
you're trying to reach.
Both the men and women
prisoners can access the medical
wing and given that Weather
forecast is a guy if he tells the
guards on duty that he's
going back To the men's prison
and he can definitely go to the
factory entrance Through the
corridor or at least that's what
he said to me you first okay
Sounds like a plan and I just
need to bribe the guards right
50 bucks enough Sure but tell
them that you need to repair
your boots at the factory no
Matter what though even if you
were able to go through the
medical wing of the Prison you'll
have to get into the courtyard
by force security is light
but If you get caught they
can shoot at you you'll get
yourself another five years For
prison breaking you think I have
to force my way in guess I'll
just have to Roll with it I
have no choice besides what's
an Additional five years to my
prison sentence it's essentially
nothing you Know thanks
for all your help Emporio sure
but I can't go further please
I want your father to come back
to life, back to consciousness,
because if he does so,
then I think we can start to see
some hope in our world again.
Shit! Aw, damn it!
What the hell is up with this can of cola?
You just touched my drink, didn't you?
Didn't you shake or touch this
can when I wasn't looking?
Well, you better go get
me a new one now, inmate!
As if.
No way I'd touch that.
The only thing I touched was
your little saucer plate.
My right shoe has a big
old hole in its heel.
Can't you see it?
It's a bit of a safety hazard.
So I'd really like to get
it repaired at the factory.
Did you not hear me?
I spilled my cola because of you!
So where's that damn towel?
Wait,
are you seriously telling me I need to
go buy you another can of soda right now?
And then I need to pour
it in your cup for you?
Come on, man, that's ridiculous.
Why don't you do this on your...
What?
What is this?
Here's what I'm looking for, a towel.
You can go now, but you have to
be back here within 20 minutes.
Huh? What the?
She's already gone?
Hang on a sec, where's my cup and saucer?
What the hell is all of this?
Could it really be?
What the?
The card saucer is floating in the air!
The cup and my boots, too!
For some reason, the cola
isn't splashing everywhere.
It's floating balls of liquid!
Every single thing I touch inexplicably
becomes unmoored, suspended in the air!
Like this $50 bill floated itself
straight out of the guard's pocket.
And even myself.
But since when?
Did all of this weird stuff begin when
that strange guy started to chase after me?
During his pursuit, he spit
some sort of substance at me.
Is that why?
The disc!
Oh no, it fell out
because my body flipped!
Stone Ocean!
Just my luck.
Why can't I control my thread?
I don't have any sense of direction.
Up or down.
There's no gravity here.
I must be in a zero-gravity
zone going to the men's prison
All right, then proceed ahead
That guy he's gonna take the desk
because I put my full strength into it.
I lost my balance
Gotta focus on this.
Go in one direction like a rocket!
Hey, what the hell?
Well, damn it, stupid disc.
I can't destroy it.
It bounces back into shape,
like some type of rubber.
That's probably the reason why Palesnake
instructed me to just
collect the disc for him.
No way!
Hey, weather forecast!
Don't go any further away from me!
Can you hear me?
I'm being attacked again!
No!
My voice doesn't reach him!
Nah, somebody got in the way.
And here I was, thinking that I was
only going to have to kill that woman,
Jolene Cujo.
Prepare for Jumpin' Jack Spark!
Weather forecast, listen!
His stand power is gravity removal!
And don't touch whatever
it is he shoots at you!
Try to dodge it, or else
you'll become weightless!
Zero gravity zone.
If you truly are a stand user, then you
should be fully aware what it is this means.
So, do you think you can figure that out?
What you've just thrown at me
looks like a piece of garbage.
This weather forecast guy,
he's apparently very powerful,
but his ability to control the
weather is still a mystery to me.
That cloud cover he summoned is probably
working as an atmospheric layer.
He simply reflected away our
enemies attack with that resistance.
And that man's arm spin
has centrifugal force.
Since it's weightless, he can accelerate
forever with that spinning force.
Which would mean, since the
core of his body stays still,
he can accurately aim with strong power.
Jumpin' Jack Spark!
No weather forecast!
Fire?
Where did this fire come from?
Air resistance friction?
This is seriously not good.
It's spreading all over my body now.
Release the zero gravity!
This is the end for you.
The abnormality alarm has
been activated in Hallway 7B.
I repeat, the abnormality
alarm... Oh shit.
Must have been the impact.
I've retrieved the damn disk and yet...
The gate is closing.
What should I do?
It's getting even harder
to go to the courtyard now.
But we have no other choice!
The enemy will be trapped in here, too!
It's my chance to get the disc!
What? No!
What in the hell?!
Everything that you touch,
if I'm right, it becomes weightless.
Am I correct?
Jolene Cujo.
The courtyard is just up ahead.
Still though, where is that
anti-gravity-wielding thief?
I need to get the disc back!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.